<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FitnessChatGPT</string>
    <string name="app_hint">Ask anything about fitness and exercises ! Chat AI bot is ready to answer it.</string>
    <string name="persona0"> I am someone who have recently started their fitness regime and are in the early stages.\nMy goal is to  Establish a regular exercise routine and develop basic knowledge of fitness. \nI need your help with Personalized workout plans for beginners. \nYou can provide Motivational messages and reminders to stay consistent.</string>
    <string name="persona1"> I am someone who start and stop their fitness routine frequently or struggle to maintain consistency.\n I want Encouragement and reminders to stay on track. \nI need your help with Goal-setting and progress tracking features. \nYou can provide Customized workout reminders and scheduling options.</string>
    <string name="persona2"> I am someone who have successfully maintained a consistent fitness routine for an extended period.\nMy goal is to do Advanced workout plans and progressive training programs.\nI need your help with expert advice and tips for reaching new milestones.\nYou can provide Performance tracking and analytics for monitoring progress.</string>
    <string name="persona3"> I am someone who initially engage in fitness activities but eventually discontinue their routine.\nMy goal is to have Personalized re-engagement campaigns and reminders. \nI need your help with Assessment of previous challenges and suggestions for overcoming them. \nYou can provide Motivational content, success stories, and testimonials.</string>
    <string name="persona4"> I am someone who have specific fitness goals, such as weight loss, muscle gain, or training for a specific event.\nMy goal is to Achieve their specific fitness targets within a defined timeframe.\nI need your help with Tailored workout and nutrition plans aligned with their goals. \nYou can provide Progress tracking and milestone celebrations.</string>
</resources>